One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
That's why we gotta cast off - together, we can!
Sailing from sea to sea,
saying it's nothing but a fairy tale.
Truth is stranger than fiction, isn't it?
Don't pretend you can't see it.
Common sense is only what the majority says it is!
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
So let's go, Captain I'll-Do-It-My-Way!
Whaddya mean, "no can do"?
We haven't even started yet!
I wanna know it all! Now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can! This moment...
We can! I can! With this feeling of freedom...
Now... Now, oh yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
Momonosuke, Heir of the Kozuki Family
Nin-nin!
I wanna see more ninjutsu! Nin-nin!
Cut the Nin-nin crap!
You already saw my ninjutsu accidentally.
Accidentally?
I know you did them for us!
Are you guys crying?
Don't be silly!
Men from the Wano Country don't cry!
It's just...
It wasn't like this when I arrived here!
The streets were bustling...
And people were living their lives!
And the whole country...
...was full of energy!
Damn those Minks!
What they did was so rash!
I will work as hard as I can to avenge you!
So forgive me!
Forgive me!
Hey, you-gara guys!
Seems like the deciphering of the stone is done!
Come back into the whale!
What do you think, Nami?
Is this what's written on the Poneglyph?
Yeah, I can draw a nautical chart based on this!
We can pinpoint the location of something, Robin!
That red stone is called a Road Poneglyph!
All the tough guys of the sea are
searching for the end of the Grand Line...
And that stone is a guide to get there!
The Whale Forest is considered sacred because of it
so it needs to be protected by us Guardians!
The end of the Grand Line...
You mean, a guide to the
last island - Raftel?!
That's right!
What?!
However...
Raftel?!
That's the goal!
To become King of the Pirates!
Finally, we can get there!
The last island - Raftel!
That's the island the flower pops mentioned!
Does it say where Raftel is?!
Wait, wait, don't jump to conclusions!
Hear me out. You see...
There are four of those red stones, the Road Poneglyphs, in the world!
What?! Does it mean there are four Raftels?!
No, there aren't! Let him finish first!
That stone must indicate the location of
some unknown spot but it's not Raftel.
The other three Road Poneglyphs all indicate
different locations in the same manner.
When you learn where those locations are
and connect those four points on a map,
those lines will cross at the center!
That's the place only the King of the Pirates and his crew have reached in all these centuries.
The last island!
The island Raftel!
The last island - Raftel!
Raftel...
Finally!
I wonder if it's there!
Or not!
The One Piece!
Okay! Let's go search!
Where are you going?! It's a big world!
I'll get back Sanji quickly!
Listen to me!
You-gara, going to Whole Cake Island along with Pekoms,
is a pretty good idea.
Of the four Road Poneglyphs,
we are missing the whereabouts of only one.
We have one here.
And the other two are
under the control of some pirates.
Pirates?
Emperor Big Mom!
And another Emperor -
Kaidou, King of the Beasts!
What?!
I see!
So we should just rob them!
Oh, I suddenly see nothing but darkness
before my eyes...
Me too!
Why?! We gotta kick their butts anyway
so let's just do it!
Don't say it like it's nothing!
I didn't care much because I thought
we wouldn't fight them anytime soon
but the thought of it makes me wet myself!
Yeah! We'll wet our pants!
Don't mess with us!
But you don't need to steal the Poneglyphs.
We don't?
Usually, people can copy their text
like making a rubbing.
No one goes around carrying around
such massive stones.
I've got an idea!
In that case, we'll sneak into
Big Mom and Kaidou's headquarters
and get the copies!
Then, we'll reach Raftel before anyone knows!
And you'll become the King of the Pirates!
What's your problem, you dummy?!
That's not manly at all!
Whoever it is, we can just kick their butts!
Easy, easy, easy!
Stop!
But I'm more worried about
you-gara, Nico Robin.
Those-gara who are interested in the Void Century.
are now collecting the copies across the world
but no one can read them.
Big names all around the world will...
...surely target you-gara and try to kidnap you when they're ready to read them.
K-Kidnap Robin?!
What?!
It's no problem.
I have strong friends who will protect me.
Whoa-whoa, did you say "Strong"?
That makes me blush!
I'll kick anyone's butt for you!
You shouldn't count on me like that...
I'll protect Robin-san no matter what!
I'll do anything for Robin too!
Super!
I won't let anyone touch Robin!
If they do, I'll take their lives and money!
They-gara are very dependable!
You have good friends.
By the way, how do you guys know
so much about the Poneglyphs?
It all started with our master -
Kozuki Oden-sama who used to
have an interest in the stones.
Because...
Is it okay to tell them, dog?
Go ahead. You don't have
to hide anything from them.
You can tell them anything.
Did you say "Go ahead"?
What's that bossy attitude?!
I am their boss! You insolent dork!
The Kozuki Family of the Wano Country was, in fact,
a clan of stonemasons that has quarried stones and processed them for generations.
They are still highly skilled.
Stonemasons?
Yes. It goes way back, 800 years ago...
The Kozuki Clan invented an indestructible book with their sophisticated skills.
That's what the Poneglyphs are!
What?!
The Kozuki Family?!
Were they the ones who made all
those Poneglyphs in the world?!
You made the stones that
Robin is looking for?!
Not me! It was my ancestors from way back!
Then, do you guys know
what's written on them?!
That hasn't been passed down fully
through the generations.
You can find it out by reading the stones.
The only thing that has been passed down was how to read and write the ancient text.
However...
Unfortunately, that's...
Before it was passed down to Momonosuke-sama,
it was cut off at his father -
Kozuki Oden-sama's generation!
By "cut off," you mean
Momonosuke-san's father is...
Yes, Oden-sama is...
Wano...
Wa...
Oden wouldn't be "oden"
if it wasn't boiled!
Hey! It's okay if you
don't wanna talk about it!
Oden-sama was...
...executed!
By the shogun of the Wano Country
and the pirate Kaidou!
What?!
To save all of us retainers,
he met his fate!
By Kaidou?!
Kaidou...
And...
...Emperor Kaidou's Beast Pirates are...
...still in the Wano Country!
In the Wano Country?
If you don't wanna talk about it,
that's okay but...
...why was your master executed?
You guys have been captured and targeted
because of that, haven't you?
Yes, you're right.
You could say it's a cardinal sin.
Kaidou is trying to pull information from us!
The previous daimyo - Kozuki Oden-sama...
...traveled to the last island Raftel
with the King of the Pirates - Gol D. Roger
and witnessed the secret of the world!
What?!
Momonosuke's father...
...went to Raftel with Gold Roger?!
Was your father one of
the Pirate King's crew?!
He witnessed the secret of the world?
Probably, with Rayleigh-san too.
Yes. We know.
We learned the entirety of history.
I see!
In order to get the secret of
the world out of you retainers,
Doflamingo and Caesar
who were tied to Kaidou...
...were trying to catch you guys.
That's right!
However...
Oden-sama didn't want to
burden us with the secret.
We don't know anything!
Yes, but even if we knew it,
we wouldn't tell anybody.
Whether we know or not,
we'll keep being hunted!
If so, the only option we have is to fight!
The words he left behind
were just one phrase!
"Open up the Wano Country!"
What do they mean by "open up"?
The Wano Country is closed off to the world.
It's a pity that, although we should have been shields for our master Oden-sama,
we were saved by him instead
and we brought shame to ourselves!
What we have to do now is
to put our lives on the
line and avenge our master!
We need to kill the shogun
who stole the Wano Country
and open the closed country to the world!
That's our wish!
The Wano Country is almost
entirely under the control
of the shogun and Kaidou who've joined forces.
Our friends are trying to
muster dissidents there now
but they're still vastly outnumbered by
the enemy's great army!
There's no chance to win!
So that's what's happening there.
But we have to win!
Thus, we set out to sea to look for allies who will fight with us.
First, we were heading for Zou!
Yes, the Kozuki Clan and the Minks
have a special bond from way back, which means whatever happens, we'll share the same fate!
More than anything, the dog and I are
Oden-sama's direct retainers.
Ever since the day Raizo arrived here,
all of our warriors were prepared!
But when we actually fought...
...it turned out like this against Jack's unit
which was just a part of Kaidou's army!
How disappointing.
What a shame.
Hey! But that's because they
used that dirty weapon!
No one could've expected
they'd use the poison gas!
If there were a judge to call foul and we'd win,
maybe that would work, but...
No matter how dirty they play,
this is our country!
We should've won!
But we won't let it happen again!
We won't repeat the same failure!
We have an ace up our sleeve too.
If we fight again, we'll show them
the true power of the Mink Tribe!
Now, we have a favor to ask, Luffy-dono!
And you too, Law-dono!
I know it's presumptuous of me to ask
you a favor after you saved my life
but I've been impressed by
how strong you guys are!
Since we are fated to share the same purpose,
will you help us fight to kill
the shogun of the Wano Country
and Emperor Kaidou?!
Oh! Yes! Who can ask for more?!
Those samurai and the Minks!
They'll be a big help for us too!
We were gonna fight Kaidou sooner or later!
We gotta jump at this chance!
They even have a ninja, Luffy!
I refuse!
Don't!
Tell me you're kidding!
Why can't you get it?!
Think about it!
We have to join hands!
Are you out of your mind?!
Just a moment! Forget about what he said!
We'll teach him a lesson!
Stop!
Luffy, think again!
This will make you less of a man!
Wait!
I think Luffy has a point there.
Nami?!
I'm gonna go...
...negotiate!
That's not it! No!
Are you just a figurehead, Momo?!
You say it!
Aren't you an important person?!
You're a leader of these
great men, aren't you?!
Are you gonna just cry?!
How could you make him cry like that?!
Don't be harsh to an eight-year old!
Luffy-san. Generally, heirs don't necessarily stand on their feet until they're fully grown.
If adults assist them properly...
Oh, Momonosuke-san?
Yes, come here, Momo-chan.
I'm sorry for what our stupid captain said to you...
You can't see it all!
And that's how the world is, Momonosuke!
Father, I...
We're surrounded!
Mother!
Ready the flaming arrows!
Run! There must be a way out!
Everyone! Run!
Your father is...
...a foolish lord!
I want to bring down Kaidou!
He was an enemy to my parents!
He killed my mother too!
I wish to grow up
and become strong quickly
and avenge my father and mother!
I want to protect all my retainers too!
Momonosuke-sama!
It's enough to know that you feel that way!
You-gara got older and weepy.
Shut up!
But because my body's still small,
I can't do that!
That's why I want you to fight with me!
I'm begging you!
Please...
I got it!
Let's join hands!
We're allies!
Let me have Kaidou's head though!
Thank you! Thank you!
You're doing it wrong!
You gotta grab tight! Like this!
Thank you!
With more energy!
But I am grabbing your hand...
No, do this!
He's right. This is how it should be.
Our leaders are bonded! This is great!
Strawhatter.
Didn't you have to ask me first?
It's cool, right?
Yeah, but...
I'm so relieved!
We have to reflect on what we were doing.
We were treating him as a child
but he is the head of the Kozuki Clan.
We were forgetting about that
and thinking we have to protect him.
Even though that was too harsh
on an eight-year old,
no one treats Momonosuke-sama
as a whole man...
...like Luffy-dono does!
Uh-huh! You're right!
Now I know why you guys admire him so much.
All right! Guys! Gather up!
Our objective is...
...to kick Emperor Kaidou's butt!
We're the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai Alliance!
That's too long!
Is "Ninja" necessary?
Of course, it is!
Okay, okay.
Our enemy is Kaidou!
Inuarashi, Nekomamushi!
Momo, Kin'emon, Kanjuro and the ninja!
And Tra-guy too!
We all join our hands to take down Kaidou!
That's what we allied for!
Guys! Don't ever bow your heads!
Nor get down on your knees!
An alliance means...
...friendship!
Not necessarily!
We're already allies
but there's one condition.
Well, isn't that something you should've told us before we agreed to join forces?!
What is the condition?
One of our crew isn't with us now.
Oh, it's about Sanji, isn't it?
Sanji?
Well, a lot has happened...
What?! Big Mom?!
I haven't heard about this!
It happened while you were sleeping.
I'll go and get him back
so don't go off to fight until then!
Is that the condition?
If so, sure, we'll wait.
Thanks! In return, Sanji will be a big help!
It's like getting help from a thousand people!
I'm worth two thousand people!
Okay, okay.
I see. Sounds like he's pretty dependable
but will you be alright?
You're talking about Emperor Big Mom!
I'm not gonna fight her so I'll be fine.
I'll go with Pekomamushi!
Pekomamushi - Lion Viper
Peko...mamushi?
Pekomamushi!
Guardians'
Residential District
Today is really a miraculous day!
Yeah! It is a great day!
Those two even split the day in half
because they didn't want to see each other
but now they're reconciled!
Yeah, it's hard to believe
that such a day has come.
They say Duke Inuarashi and Master Nekomamushi
were once closest friends.
However when they came back
from a long journey barely alive,
they were already deep in a feud.
Every time they came face-to-face,
they'd try to kill each other.
I wonder what happened...
That was before I was born, right?
Yes. Even Pedro and I
were small at that time.
Let's have a banquet to celebrate the reconciliation of our kings today!
We can wake up and go to bed anytime we like!
Target confirmed, Jack-sama!
Yeah, I see it. You don't have to tell me.
Damn. I can't believe I came back here.
Sheepshead.
"Raizo wasn't there."
I didn't expect you to come back saying that.
The Minks have a strong vital force.
What if those who escaped the gas
were able to treat the others who passed out?
Keep your mouth shut, Sheepshead-sama!
If he finds out that not only are the Minks alive but also that we were kicked off the island by someone...
When you start killing someone, don't stop until he dies!
Mercy will only cause
the messy business of revenge!
You don't need to worry!
The Minks are weakening anyway.
If we make a raid, they'll just...
That's not necessary.
We'll kill the giant elephant!